Visit our website for more: turkision.com
No living being was harmed during the
filming of this series.
Episode 114
Olof
Olof!
I took the castle you love so much
from you.
Now...
Did you come to beg me to
take your soul too?
I swear I will hang you on
these walls of İnegol.
You will pay for every
drop of blood you shed.
You can't do anything.
Even if you attack me with all your
strength...
You will die under these
walls, Turgut.
Do you think we are
afraid of martyrdom?
I, Turgut Bey, will make this world hard for
you, even if it's the last moments of my life.
No.
You and your Alps will not live long.
My valiant.
Don't worry, my Bey
I'm going towards martyrdom.
Don't do it, Olof.
Don't.
My brother.
Everyone who stands up
against Jesus' army...
I will cut off their head.
This bloody dream that you dream of...
will be the end of you all.
Know that the Turks will fight
until none of you is left.
And we will fight.
Don't waste your breath, Turgut.
You will need it for your
last-minute begging.
Shields!
I'll come, Olof.
I will come soon.
You may hide behind the walls of the
castle as you wish, but I will come.
I will come to tear down
these walls over your head.
Come on!
Let's go!
Let's go.
I hope Turgut Bey does
nothing wrong when he is angry.
We've seen what happened when he's moved
without Osman Bey's knowledge recently.
He won't, especially when it's like this.
Osman Bey is coming.
Alps are ready, my Bey, and
they await your orders.
Nobody will move.
Let them wait ready.
Olof and İsmihan.
Now, they'll think we're
going to attack İnegöl.
But we will stop.
Konur.
Tell us what information
you have on İnegöl.
They took advantage of Turgut
Bey's absence, my Bey.
But this is not the only reason.
It seems that the
traitors are among us.
Traitors are on the
job of protecting the castle.
They are the ones
who sell their honor for money.
What are you saying?
They let Olof take the castle.
Look at those dog breeds.
Sorry, my Bey.
Ignobles.
We are fighting a fierce
war with the enemy.
My Allah
Save us from the evil of
the hypocrites.
Boran.
You will find them all and
bring them to me.
They walk around as warriors, my Bey.
I'll go and see.
I will know everyone who put
money in his pocket unjustly.
Then, we will hold them all accountable.
My Bey, do you think Olof
and İsmihan move together?
If Olof stays free...
He may have handed his
collar over to İsmihan.
But when my sword
touched İsmihan's neck...
I saw in her eyes that she didn't know
anything about İnegöl.
Olof may have moved on his own.
Whether he cooperated
with her or he was alone.
It'll be the same in both cases.
What are we going to do, Osman Bey?
Can I come in, my Bey?
Come in.
My Bey, Şamil has sent word from Konya.
Naiman.
He entered Konya with his army.
Jesus' great units...
will be waiting at İnegöl ready.
Turgut.
He'll knock on our door with Osman.
Their anger will make them taste defeat.
If Turgut doesn't attack...
Turgut must have gone
mad with anger.
He will attack.
If they don't attack, we will attack them
What about İsmihan?
What would you say about this?
İsmihan.
Stop.
Olof!
How dare you move
without an order from me!
Mother Sultan.
I've been waiting for you.
Are you waiting for your death?
You will pay for this insolence.
I'm not the one who will pay the price.
It was paid by those who killed
Kantakuzenos and my men.
I broke the neck of those
who don't obey us.
I will continue to do this.
İnegöl is the beginning.
I will take everything Osman
owns from him...
for you.
This place is yours, Mother Sultan..
Naiman.
He will rest there first.
Then, he will attack us
with all his brutality.
Osman Bey, how big is his army?
We have eliminated a lot of them.
About 40 thousand.
They outnumber us.
My Bey.
Let's go to Konya.
We reduce their number more and more.
And then, in a place we
know, near Yenişehir...
We gather our strength again
and pounce on them.
No.
This is not a heavy Byzantine army.
They are the Mongols.
You can't survive even if you run away.
Their military units
are just like ours
They must have
mounted archers.
Is there no solution, my Bey?
No, there is definitely a solution.
We trusted solution of those
who didn't have a solution.
Yes, our war is one.
But we are different from them.
Our breasts are filled with faith
and the gentle light of Allah.
- Boran.
- My Bey.
Bring that map.
Bring it.
Now.
40 thousand people.
They will get from this point
to here in 5 days.
- Boran.
- My Bey.
Let those who are ready
for martyrdom have units of their own.
They are the ones
who will find the way.
They are the ones who will slow them down.
Your command, my Bey.
We need 7 days.
These units will not return, my Bey.
Let them go out on
their way knowing it.
The existence of great nations is
associated with the horseless heroes.
- Boran.
- My Bey.
Send a message to everyone.
Let the preparations begin.
Will the defense strategy
we are building be sufficient, my Bey?
This campaign is not to stop
them, but to slow them down.
Bala, you'll be at the helm of
the sisters, and you'll dig ditches.
You will control the roads
and cross all the bridges.
Everyone who can do anything
will be with you.
Do not worry.
I will go out on my way.
Your soul is in my hands, Olof.
If you breathe again
without even asking my permission...
I will bury you and your men in one grave.
We'll bury in this grave those who stand
against us, Mother Sultan.
You made Osman weak.
I made him weaker.
There's nothing left
but to cut his neck.
We'll cut it off when
the time is right.
Turgut has come as far
as the walls of İnegöl.
He understood that he would not
be able to take the castle alone.
He will attack with Osman soon.
Then I will rip out their livers.
I won't hold you back, Olof...
until you bring me the heads of Osman
and Turgut and throw them in front of me
But you will not harm the people
of İnegöl.
I do not stand by those who
cause injustice to the people.
The Christian and Muslim people
of İneöl live in peace.
None of them will be harmed.
My Sultan.
What's the matter, Avcı Bey?
Naiman's army has reached
Konya, My Sultan.
Tell me every step they take.
I'm going now, Olof.
Take care of my city.
But my shadow will always be here.
Yakup Bey...
Karesi Bey...
And Candar Bey.
I'll check out all of their states.
And we will make all the tribes revolt.
The love of Jihad in our
hearts is not enough.
We will call all tribes to fight.
However...
We'll start first with Candar Bey.
He is the closest person to our cause.
My Bey, didn't Candar Bey
express his devotion to the Mother Sultan?
It will be difficult to convince him.
When it comes to the homeland of the Turks,
there is no doubt that he will be next to us.
We have a very important piece in
our hands to convince him.
What if he is not convinced? What if he
doesn't stand behind us?
These lands are Naiman's goal, and
few of them will stand against him.
Either we all live or we all perish.
We will make it very clear to them that
if we perish, they will perish as well.
When they gathered in the palace, they wanted
to be busy with trade, money and gold.
None of them will show
any willingness to resist.
My Bey, will the army that will be
formed be able to convince them to resist?
This war will be greater than the war
that will take place on the battlefield.
We will make them fight at their will.
We will ignite the fires
of faith in their hearts.
Then not only will they have been convinced,
but they will have believed in this cause.
When they believe in this cause, they
will not only be able to...
resist the Mongols, but
we will pursue them to Tabriz.
We just need to
succeed in this campaign.
- Inshallah, my Bey.
Inshallah, my Bey.
Inshallah, but...
What if Turgut Bey attacks İnegöl and
opens another front on us from the west?
- Can I come in, my Bey?
- Come in.
Turgut Bey has come, my Bey.
Let him in.
Leave me and Turgut alone,
there are things I will talk to him about.
Marmaracık Castle
Allah bless you...
and that marriage.
You two agreed to
marry my sister, Alçiçek.
Thank you, Bayındır.
Thank you.
- May Allah bless you.
- Thank you.
Inshallah, you can hold your wedding before
the forty thousand Mongol soldiers come.
Bayındır, don't talk about bad things.
Mother Sultan is the one who stands
for this good deed.
May Allah be pleased with her.
What would we do if
we didn't have Mother Sultan?
From now on, he's your brother-in-law, of
course, but I'll tell you something.
You know it was all planned by
Osman, right?
He beheaded the soldiers
and brought upon us the scourge of Nayman.
40,000 soldiers.
Our situation will be difficult if
they come to the border areas.
Is there room for this possibility
anymore, Öktem Bey?
Beys of the great Beyhoods
have left after hearing of this.
Who would want to antagonize Nayman?
Osman's arrogance has caused us trouble.
Who's in trouble is obvious, Bayındır Bey.
Osman's head is what will be burned.
Mother Sultan will not allow
the border areas to be destroyed.
She's able to rein in
Neiman and Osman.
She will definitely tell us
what we should do.
Can I come in, my Bey?
Come in, Aybars.
Mother Sultan is coming.
Go ahead.
I went to the place where I'd meet
with my warriors.
But none of them ever came.
And no one came from the castle.
My warriors do not flee, Osman Bey.
And I know that if they are not
prisoners, they are all martyrs.
I know.
I saw them with my own eyes.
Olof has surrounded
the outskirts of the castle.
They even do guard tours.
What's worse is...
that the observers came and told me...
that İsmihan...
went to İnegöl right after us.
She cooperates with
the infidels, Osman Bey.
İsmihan, who used to tell us, "Let's
unite against the Mongols."
It is clear that she has orchestrated
the traitors on the inside.
She went to inegöl in a hurry.
Maybe...
She went to hold Olof accountable for
taking the castle without her knowledge.
Turgut.
Things are bad now.
Things got mixed up.
Even if he took İnegöl
without İsmihan's will...
that will benefit her.
Now, İsmihan and Olof are
waiting for us there.
This is what it looks like.
Let them wait.
But we won't go.
Why won't we go?
We will stop.
We will not attack.
Our standing will drive them crazy.
They'll get mad the longer we wait.
They're used to us always showing up
and fighting them off on some side.
We won't.
As long as we don't fight them, they'll wait
longer to see where we will hit them.
Until when?
Don't worry.
They will be destroyed.
We will destroy them!
What did Allah say?
Yet their various groups have differed
among themselves about him,
so woe to the disbelievers when
they face a tremendous Day!
When they differ among themselves...
Only then will I overthrow
them with the sword of justice!
Justice will not be achieved with
those dogs except with the sword!
When I stop...
You will stop too.
Don't worry.
İnegöl won't stay like this.
Now...
if Naiman comes to us...
and if we act like this...
It will only tire us out.
Yes.
As I lost all those Alps...
I know I don't have a chance for that.
Oh.
Since I moved without you...
Many calamities befell us.
From now on, I will do as you say.
Your command.
Tell me die and I will die now.
Thank you.
I'm going out on the road now.
I will return with a
large army, Inshallah.
Welcome, my Sultan.
Thank you, Öktem Bey.
It seems that the news of the army that
reached Konya has also come to you.
The calamity brought by Osman...
hit us all.
There are 40,000 Mongol
soldiers, Mother Sultan.
Maybe more.
If you collect all the swords in
the border, it will not be equal to them.
Forgive me, Mother Sultan.
But how do we stop them?
What we will do is clear.
We must unite to stop Naiman and his army.
I have the power to secure that union.
Öktem Bey, Bengi Hatun.
You two will take care of the caravans.
That hungry flock will
attack the caravans first.
Security is important.
As you command, Mother Sultan.
What about İnegöl?
We're not going to leave it in
Olof's hands.
If we don't stop Nayman...
we won't not just lose İnegöl...
we'll lose everything, Bengi Hatun.
Mother Sultan.
Don't scare us with death so
we can accept concessions.
The homeland is a homeland
and the infidels are infidels.
We're not leaving İnegöl for Olof.
All I've done up to this day...
explains what I will do.
Don't have any doubts.
You can go back to your work now.
Bayındır Bey.
You stay.
What should I do?
Tell me, what should I do?
You will stay here.
Take care of the tribe.
Olof, who will see we
haven't moved yet...
may launch a move.
For this reason...
We cannot lose another property.
I will not allow the infidels to take
another inch of our lands anymore.
Don't worry.
You will return with a
huge army, Inshallah.
Don't worry.
I will go now.
You will go to your duty.
And we will win, Inshallah.
We will win.
You will go to Germiyanids, Jandarids
and Karesi Beys.
You will tell them that Mother Sultan is
preparing a huge army against the Naiman.
I have to know how loyal they are to me.
I can only trust you
for this, Bayındır.
The sun of the upper
Seljuk state.
Mother Sultan.
Don't worry at all.
All Beys will unite
behind you against Naiman.
Bayındır will solve this.
Alçiçek.
Are you going on a mission?
Yes.
What about you?
Ayşe Hatun summoned me...
for wedding preparations.
But I'm afraid that
something bad will happen again.
They say the Mongols are coming.
And İnegoöl is in the hands of
the infidels.
Don't be afraid, Alçiçek Hatun.
We will solve everything, Inshallah.
And we will hold our marriage well.
Inshallah.
Be careful.
Go and come back safely.
I leave such a beauty behind me.
How can I not come back!
Come on.
See you.
Germinyanids
Yakup Bey's Palace
Do you see, Yakup Bey...
the calamity that Osman brought to us?
Fear does not prevent death, Karesi Bey.
You...
Are you on the last frontier?
You should be the last to worry.
Do I only care about the
lives of my tribe members?
All the oppressed will be
crushed by the oppressors
Whoever caused this calamity
is the one who will pay it for us.
Are we going to leave Mother Sultan
alone too?
We will not leave anyone alone.
I will not leave these
lands to the Mongols.
And I will not allow
Osman to gather strength.
How will you do this?
Can I come in, my Bey?
My Bey, the presents
for Commander Naiman are ready.
60 horses will carry them.
We're waiting for your command to get
on the road.
Let them get on the road immediately.
Get to Naiman before Naiman gets
here.
The Messenger himself will
deliver these to Naiman.
May Neiman know well
our respect for him.
Your command, my Bey.
Yakup Bey.
In your opinion, is it possible to get
out of this problem through one letter?
I say we draw swords and fight.
My son-in-law.
When you are young and have a big heart...
You want to solve all
matters by the sword.
But blood is not shed in a matter
that can be resolved by words.
We'll see if the letter will work.
Otherwise, our situation
will be miserable.
But I will not allow Osman
to bring this calamity upon us...
and not to come out of here as a winner.
You take Osman
too seriously.
Karesi Bey.
One day a villager came to the palace...
He looked and found a big meeting
and all the dignitaries were there.
He shouted at the top of his voice:
"I will be the Sultan one day!"
Everyone giggled.
Sultan was the only one who did not laugh.
He was the only one who had
grief, did you know?
What does that mean?
It means that Osman wants
to rule this region.
He wants to be chief of the
tribes and leader of the Turks.
That is, the position he has set his
sights on is not yours to take seriously.
The position he has
set his sights on is mine.
Come on, I made them prepare a
table in honor of your visit.
Let's all sit together.
Köprühisar
Why did you bother?
You can start.
You came from the road, you must be tired.
I'm coming right away.
We are grateful to you.
Let us go now.
Let's not bother you anymore.
No, it is not permissible, you are
my guests now.
I will not leave you.
Come on, start at once and
don't let it get cold, come on.
Thank you.
We...
Cerkutay, here we come to
Köpruhisar, what are we going to do now?
Are you asking what we will do?
We'll get out of this house one way.
Let's get out, you, but you talk too
much, that man will not let us go!
Hey says stay and sleep here!
He found a man like me, and
of course he loved me.
Yes, of course he loves you!
Who doesn't love you, right?
Good, well, you're right.
Let's get out of this house as soon as possible,
but how are we going to get rid of this man?
This doesn't concern me anymore.
When my Osman Bey
asks you tomorrow...
You can say "We went as spies but one of the men loved me so much we couldn't get out of the house."
Okay!
- Father! Father!
- Shut up! Shut up!
Cerkutay, leave the boy.
I let him, but he does
not let me.
My son, my little one, leave him.
Father!
Get in, run, run!
My Father.
Father! They're running away.
I have to do this for my sister.
I can't do this, it's too bad.
No, it is not permissible.
You will, Esma. It is the order of
the Mother Sultan.
Don't forget, you're putting poison on
Aladdin's training sword.
When the poison mixes with his blood, the
brother will have killed his brother.
Please, don't.
I told you to do that!
You will set fire to Yenişehir's palace.
Well, what is this poison?
Will he kill him?
It's enough to do what I said, don't
get involved.
And what about Bengi Hatun?
What do you say about this?
The Mother Sultan and Bengi
Hatun know about it.
If you don't do what I say, you
will never see your sister again.
I tidied the place.
Here you go, I brought you a drink, too.
Thank you, Esma.
Enjoy it.
Thank you, Esma sister.
Sit down, brother.
Enjoy it.
We rusted a lot.
Let's practice tomorrow, what
do you think bro?
Let's do it, brother.
Cerkutay this is a dead end.
What are we going to do now?
We'll take care of ourselves, Hatun.
Oh, Ülgen Hatun.
Leave it to me.
I'll solve it now, I'll solve it now.
Stop it, leave it to me.
If we knock, maybe they'll open.
Go away, Hatun.
O Allah!
It's open!
Damn it, are you okay?
Spread fast, find them.
It's a dead end, look everywhere.
Are they gone?
They spread around.
But we have to wait for
nightfall to get out.
Thanks to me, we survived, Ülgen Hatun.
Yes, so be safe, may Allah
be pleased with you.
I don't know how we would have got
through the open door if it weren't for you.
You're welcome.
You are the best spy I've ever seen.
Thank you.
Yes, what are we going to do now?
We'll wait.
We'll find a way
into the castle at nightfall.
You thought that well.
The boy bit me.
Let me look.
Oh! He really did it.
He did.
What did you say?
What did I say?
Olof crossed the line with,
what he did lately, Frigg.
He went out of my way.
He said things I couldn't believe.
He converted to Christianity.
He's going to do all his moves
for the religion of Jesus anymore.
Yes, Mother Sultan.
Damned Kantakuzenos.
All these works are of his own design.
Olof turned his back on Odin.
Who turns their back on Odin today...
turns his back on
you and me tomorrow, Frigg.
Mother Sultan.
Olof gives up on everyone,
but he can't give up on me.
Don't be so confident.
Wasn't he giving his life
for Odin yesterday?
Yes.
Who does not show
loyalty towards his religion...
will never show loyalty to you, Frigg.
Men are like that.
He must have found
a Christian girl by now.
Mother Sultan.
That will be the end of him.
He can't risk this.
You trust Olof a lot, Frigg.
But my opinion is that
he is a two-faced man.
My advice to you is that you
reconsider your loyalty to him again.
I'm saying this for you, Frigg.
You can go now.
Frigg won't leave Olof anymore.
From now on, neither of them
would do anything without my knowledge.
Avcı Bey.
Send news to our Sultan.
He should write a letter to the Beys of Jandarids
and Karasids asking them to be on my side.
He should send it with gifts.
Shall we send gifts to Germiyanids, too?
Prepare my horse.
- Bring it, bring it, let's see.
- Enjoy it.
In the Name of Allah., the Most
Gracious, the Most Merciful.
Aktemur.
Give it to them.
Gürbüz
Wait.
Eat.
In the name of Allah.
Mashallah, it's very tasty, Torahan.
- Thank you.
- May Allah be pleased with you, my Bey.
We became witnesses to
Gürbüz's hunting skill, but...
How did you catch it so fast?
What's the secret?
I watch the separated from the flock, my
Bey, you taught me that.
Yes, you are right.
This is the end of those who do not like
union and think of separation.
The same situation, whether
in humans or animals.
We will not allow anyone to
leave the herd.
Inshallah.
- We will overcome all of this.
- Inshallah, my Bey.
Here.
İnegöl Castle
Accept these gifts from us as a token
of our friendship, Commander Naiman.
From the ruler of İnegöl, the
great Commander Olof.
Get the chests and presents to Commander
Naiman as quickly as possible.
Tell Dan to bring the nuns and the priest
from the monastery in Köprühisar.
I will make this place the
center of Christianity.
Collect the boxes.
I wonder if Odin laughs at you.
Or will he spit on you?
Frigg.
My love.
From now on, I will begin to serve
Jesus' great debt.
I do whatever I have to do.
I sometimes think...
how you have remained
loyal to me until now?
He who changes his God also
changes his lover.
Isn't that right, Olof?
Have I been caught?
Christian girls in İnegöl are pretty...---
You remember what I did to you, right?
Don't trust my love that much.
I ignored your betrayal of your religion.
And?
If you are not loyal to me, you will
not have an eye to see.
Frigg.
My lover.
I got the place Nikola lost back.
I came and took the place
most valuable to the Turks.
All this happened...
by entering into the religion of Jesus.
I will extend my roots here.
Extend your roots?
You spread
your roots on your own, right?
Or with those beautiful
Christian girls?
Together.
Together, my love.
I would never do it without you.
We have Byzantine...
and Mongols to support us.
We will grow up.
We'll grow old, my love.
We will grow up a lot.
A lot.
Jandarids Tribe
Candar Bey's Palace
What is this caftan for?
A Bey like you, who is with Majesty Mother
Sultan and Majesty Sultan Alaeddin...
deserves a glamorous caftan like this.
This is why.
Thank you.
Thank you...
however...
who said we are with them?
You collected gifts in front of me.
How much of this money here is worth the
blood of the fighters when we go to war?
Do they measure everything you have
in gold, Bayındır Bey?
What's this?
Don't talk like you are our enemy.
You insult us.
Our only goal is the future of our
homelands and our followers.
People like you only think
of their own interests.
You don't think about homeland or people.
These are the last things people
like you think about.
Know that you knocked on the wrong door.
Oh, the great Candar Bey.
Yesterday you were waiting at
the door of the palace...
today, you have become the
owner of a homeland.
You can't turn your back on the Seljuqs
who have deigned you with all this.
If you do...
Sultan Aladdin will not forget this.
Are you threatening me in
my presence, Bayındır Bey?
I will now forgive you to show
such manner in front of the Mongols too.
Candar Bey.
Mother Sultan asks you to join
the army she will establish.
You know very well that the Mother Sultan
always gets what she wants.
So, she said, remind him of it if
he will not be persuaded.
Who gave you your country?
Yes, Sultan Mesut gave it to you.
He can take everything you have
in one command as he gave it to you...
Candar Bey.
Don't let me finish the rest.
Don't sleep and die, my Candar
Bey, get up and die!
Participate in the army that
Mother Sultan will establish.
Wave your sword against the
infidels, come on!
I've reclaimed my homeland with the strength
of my wrists and the blood of my brave men.
No one has ever looked to
me for my services.
They called me Yaman Jandar. (yaman=tough)
If you threaten me and try to force me
to do something with threats...
Dig a grave for yourself.
However...
Protecting our homeland
is our job.
I will think carefully and write a letter
to Mother Sultan my decision.
You can go out.
Allah is the greatest.
Peace and mercy of Allah.
Oh my Allah...
You are the one and you are the one.
Our cause is to spread your
call to the whole world.
My Allah.
- Make our way a victory.
- Amin.
You are the one who will protect us from
the unbelievers, the hypocrites...
and the secret and over traps, my Allah.
We turn to you, my Allah.
My Allah.
Our goal is for the nation to unite...
and to raise your word
and spread it throughout the world...
not on individual issues, but for you.
My Allah.
Our money and possessions
are sacrificed for your sake.
Amin.
My Allah, don't let me and those
who pray to you and...
all believers be seduced by themselves.
Amin.
My Allah.
Make my words count.
Make it effective.
Grant us the strength that enables
us to expel the infidels.
Accept our prayers, my Allah.
Amin.
Mother Sultan.
What's up, Celali?
What's Naiman's plan?
As you commanded, we've been watching
Naiman since his arrival in Tabriz, Mother Sultan.
Things are not good at all.
You must have heard of
Naiman's arrival in Konya.
I heard it.
What is the attitude of my son, Sultan
Aladdin, towards Naiman?
Sultan Alaeddin,
for the protection of Konya,
is respectful.
But in order to protect the borders, he tries
to distract him in Konya as much as he can.
Naiman is like a bloodthirsty
wolf, Mother Sultan.
He is not distracted by training
or entertainment.
He wants to walk to the border at once.
I'll have the Beys behind me
before he gets to the border.
What's Naiman's war plan?
Naiman is smart.
He will divide his army.
The army will reach these
lands within days.
But Naiman won't be at their helm.
What does this mean, Celali?
Naiman is the strongest warrior that has
ever come to this land, my Sultan.
He knows that Beys will unite.
In order to stop them, he
will pretend to come...
but he will go north first.
He knows that Beys in the
north have lost their power.
He will destroy the Jandarids first...
and then, Chobanids.
And so, he will destroy us
before we can unite.
Then, we shall win our move before he
reaches the border, Celali.
Otherwise...
There is not a single inch
of land that we give to the infidels.
Until we get İnegöl back, which is ours...
whoever comes before us...
either we die...
or we kill them.
- Acar.
- Yes, my Bey.
What is the status of the Alps?
They you ready.
Good.
Kutan is coming, my Bey.
My Bey.
Tell me about Olof's men.
Are they large in number?
Olof is taking this seriously.
His men are strayed, but...
They are crowded.
It doesn't matter even if
he brings his whole army!
We have no solution but to attack.
Come on valiants!
Kopru Hisar
Why did you come?
I wish I had come alone
I don't know whether to protect you
or gather information.
You should have told this to Osman Bey!
Don't protect me, I'll protect myself!
Protect yourself first.
Come on, come on, come on.
We'll take the priests and monks
from the monastery
Olof is starting his regime in Ingol.
Everything will be reworked.
The church will be repaired.
Get your supplies ready,
we'll take them to Inegol.
To Inegol that we took
from foolish Turks!
Inegol will only be your grave.
What do we do now, Cerkutay?
They even took Inegol while we
still strive here!
Ulgen Hatun.
Hear what I'm going to say...
...before you draw everyone here.
Osman Bey knew the tricks
played by the infidels
Our plan changed.
We're going to Inegol now.
But Osman Bey ordered us to
go to Kopruhisar.
The infidels were all in
Kopruhisar back then.
Now they're in Inegol.
Our mission here is over.
Good, but how do we enter Inegol?
We need two robes.
A robe of nun and a priest.
Okay.
Let's go.
Olof will take your life.
Don't you worry.
Soon.
He will end up like you.
Neiman's coming from the east.
Even if he surrounds us,
we won't leave Olof alone
The moment he walks out of the castle...
...we'll deny his life!
Come on, alps!
Oh Allah, forgive me, Allah.
I can't stand it
Don't let a brother kill his brother, Esma.
Brother.
I'm fine brother
It's a small scratch.
Hey, let's continue.
Drink this, brother
I'm fine brother.
Aladdin.
I can't move my hand.
Brother, your hand is hot as fire
Come on, let's see
Kumral Abdal right away!
Come on, come on.
What will happen?
What will the poison do?
Do you think Candar Bey
will be with us, my Bey?
Candar is the weakest link.
I saw it in his eyes
He is never afraid
He trusts his alps.
He heard of Nayman, but...
...he doesn't care at all.
He must have a secret power, my Bey.
Otherwise, why would
he speak so fearlessly?
I do not know about that.
All I know is if Osman cooperates with him...
Mother Sultan will cut off our heads.
What are we going to do, my Bey?
It doesn't matter if he manages
to convince Candar or not.
As long as Karasi and Germiyan
are with us...
Candar is of no importance at all.
We will save our heads
We'll convince them first.
No.
Rather, we will prevent Osman
from convincing them.
Karasi Bey's son-in-law.
What was his name?
Uslu.
Uslu Bey.
Yes, Uslu Bey.
Let's see if Karasi Bey will agree
to work with Osman...
...when he hears his son-in-law
is killed by Osman.
You are going to set a fire,
huh my Bey?
Fire it is.
It's going to be such a fire...
We will throw dry woods in that fire.
Candarogullari Beyship
Candar Bey's Mansion
Our armies are getting ready...
And when the time comes...
...under the command of Mother Sultan...
Can I come in, my Bey?
Come!
Osman Bey arrived.
He wants to talk.
In difficult times the demand for
the brave increases.
Let the letter wait.
Let's listen to Osman Bey.
Let him come.
Peace be upon you.
Peace be upon you too, Osman Bey.
-Welcome.
-Thank you.
Thank you.
What do we owe this pleasure?
Bayindir Bey, who came before us...
...must have told you
the reason for our visit.
And you also came to tell me
to support Mother Sultan then?
No.
I want you to support me.
What a shame.
Bayindir Bey at least offered presentsç
As for you, you came empty-handed and
with a commanding tongue
Too bad.
I see they showered you with gifts.
Thinking they will buy your army.
They covered you with gold.
In addition...
They think they will take advantage of you.
They dressed you in a luxurious caftan
Osman Bey!
Thank Allah I've got everything ready
for my Alcicek.
...don't get me wrong, Ayse Hatun...
...but I guess you haven't had any
preparaitons for Aktemur's marriage.
Bengi Hatun.
I sewed them all
one by one with my own hands.
Paying money and buying them
from the market is easy.
I sewed my son's supplies
with my own hands.
Bless you, Ayse Hatun.
They are all very beautiful.
Thank you, my daughter.
They are all so beautiful.
Esma, collect them.
Our daughter Alcicek liked it too.
Thank you for your efforts, my Ayse!
As long as hearts are connected,
other shortcomings will surely be handled.
Why would you say that, Bengi Hatun?
I'll go for a fresh air.
Mother!
Aladdin, what happened?
- My brother.
- What happened to your brother?
Orhan!
Orhan, what happened?
It's nothing, mother.
Don't worry.
Aladdin is exaggerating.
How did this happen?
I injured him during the training.
It's not important, brother.
But his forearm burns like fire.
He can't even hold a sword.
Malhun.
This can't be caused by a sword.
There must be something else.
What is that?
Poison?
The weapon wound cannot shape
like this in a short time.
Call Kumral Abdal at once.
Aladdin, son.
Bring your sword but don't touch
the blade, okay?
My Orhan, come sit here.
Did you do this?
Candar Bey.
I appreciate you.
And I know how great you are.
I know that...
Candar Bey cannot be deceived by
gold or caftan.
A faithful one cannot be deceived.
I want you to fight with me
against the infidels.
What do they want?
Do they have other intentions other than
fighting the infidels?
And they're creating an army, too.
Everyone is looking
to strengthen themselves!
You are correct.
I want to be stronger.
But I don't want to be rich like they do.
Did you hear the latest events?
I lost my castles.
Inegol, Yenisehir...
And Sogut.
I lost all of them.
After all those conquests...
...I came back to my tents.
Why?
Tell me, why?
Not to bow down to Mother Sultan.
If I obeyed her...
...I would have been richer
and wealthier.
If my only aim was money and power...
...I wouldn't choose this way.
I am not the same with them.
I am a Turkish Bey who thinks only of
the interest of the innocents.
And I...
I consider you one of us.
For this reason,
I am asking you to stand with me.
Supporting you means...
...confronting Sultan Aladdin
with everything he has
What about Germiyan?
What about Karasi?
What if they choose the opposite?
If they choose the opposite...
I will only be joining your loneliness,
Osman Bey.
The path is tough.
Few heroes walk these paths.
You need a decision.
Tell me.
Are you loyal to...
Sultan Aladdin?
Or are you loyal to Sultan Mesut?
The one who gave you
everything is Sultan Mesut.
You sound like Bayindir Bey.
Sultan Mesut is dead.
There is no one left who can protect you.
Sultan Aladdin will end you.
No, no.
They lie to you.
Sultan Mesut is alive.
He asks you to support me.
Prove it.
Here.
This ring.
You must have seen this ring
when you kissed Sultan Mesut's hand.
The future of your Beyship
depends on the decision you will make.
You need Sultan Mesut
on this difficult path.
Sultan Mesut also said he'd support you
in the conquest of Kastamonu...
...which you have beeen dreaming to have.
Now...
Will you stand on the side of falsehood...
...or on the right side?
Make up your mind.
Burn this caftan!
Don't let his misfortune spread among us!
Your command, my Bey!
Wait, Malhun, let's care Orhan,
now is not the time
- I ask you! Did you do this?
- Stop it, Malhun Hatun.
Why would I do this?
Why would I be here then?
I thought there was no enmity between
us anymore! I gave you my daughter!
If you come out behind this...
I swear to you that I will kill you myself.
I didn't do it.
Now leave me alone
and take care of your son.
Hurry up, Komral Abdul!
Tell me, what's his situation, Komral Abdul?
- Where's the sword?
- Here.
Orhan.
What happened, Komral Abdul?
The sword is poisoned
But I'm fine.
There is no pain,
I just feel like my hand is burning
The poison is spreading, Orhan Bey.
But it will show its effects slowly.
We don't know how it will affect you.
You'll be fine, son, you'll be fine.
We don't have much time left.
My Bey, if we go through the valley,
we will buy more time
- Lead the way, we'll follow you.
- Yes my Bey.
Enough, Bengi Hatun, I've had enough
Kill me so that I get rid of this!
Wait Esma, what the hell?
I told what you said!
You saw it!
How are we going to pay
for this sin?
What are you saying, Esma?
I do not understand anything!
What did you do?
What does it have to do with me?
Why are you playing the fool?
You said you didn't do it there!
But you gave me the order.
I put that poison.
Silent!
Do you hear what you're saying, Esma?
Now lower your voice and
explain this well.
What happened?
Come on.
How is this possible?
How do you not know?
Know what?
- But they told me that you...
- What?
- They said you wanted this?
- I wanted what?
Avci Bey came and he said he'd kill my brother
if I don't do what he says.
He said Bengi Hatun wanted it.
Ismihan.
He'll be fine, won't he, Kumaral Abdul?
If Allah permits.
If we find the poison,
we will also find the cure.
We will definitely find it.
I sent Alcicek and Bengi.
If this wasn't Bengi Hatun...
...who was it to come into our tent
and put the prison on the sword?
Who would dare do such a thing?
Only Ismahan can do this.
But how?
Obviously, there is a traitor among us.
Yes there is.
Did someone enter the tent
without your consent, Aladdin?
Think well.
Is there someone you suspect?
My Orhan, haven't you seen anyone?
No.
It happened because of me
No son, not because of you
...they're trying to
set us against each other, but...
We are going to spoil this game.
You will be fine.
Give it to me, brother.
Come on, drink a little.
What's going on, Orhan?
Mother.
I can't raise my hand, mother.
Kumral Abdal.
Do something Kumral Abdal!
Kumral Abdal I don't feel my arm!
- Kumral Abdal!
- Do something Kumral Abdal.
Kumral Abdal!
I don't feel it, Kumral Abdal!
Will I ever hold sword again?
Mother!
Mother Bala!
Will I ever hold sword again, mother?
Mother, where are you going?
Mother!!
- Say something mother!
- Hold on my valiant!
-Don't leave me like this, Mother Bala!
-We'll find a way.
Heal me!
- We'll find the cure.
- Say something mother!
Mother!
Bala Mother! Don't let this happen!
Calm down, Orhan.
Don't let it happen, Kumral Abdal!
Kumral Abdal!
Mother!
Karasiogugullari Beyship
Karesi Mansion
Osman Bey, the rebel Bey.
What brings you to our land?
Or are you seeking protection
from the Mongols?
Man does not run away from fight.
Rather, we stand like iron in front of
those who brought fire to this earth
We do not bow our heads,
we make them bow.
They say the Mongols have reached
Konya, Osman Bey.
Let's see if you can keep this manner
in front of them.
My side is apparent.
Rather, you are the ones who
must choose your side
Karasi Bey is waiting for you.
This way.
It happened because of me.
I caused this, brother.
Because of me.
It is not your fault, my brother.
You have no fault at all.
I caused this.
I hurt you.
I poisoned you.
I did this.
Come to your senses, Aladdin!
Now go investigate everyone
in the tribe and find out who did this, come on.
I'm going to find out who did this, brother.
I will find them.
Drink this, Orhan Bey,
it'll heal you inshallah.
Inshallah!
O Healer!
(one of Allah's names)
In the name of Allah, the Most Gracious,
the Most Merciful.
Heal him, my Allah.
Can this Priest Hristo be trusted?
Will he help us, Cerkutay?
Priest Hristo helped us a lot
in Inegol.
He must have set off as soon as
he got the compass.
Osman Bey values Priest Hristo a lot.
I hope so.
He is coming.
For the sake of Jesus Christ! I have prepared
your place as soon as I read the letter you sent
I knew that Osman Bey would not leave
Inegol in the hands of those oppressors.
Olof called all the priests and nuns
to Inegol.
Let us enter like we are one of you.
I obey Osman Bey's orders surely.
Now put on these clothes.
No one will suspect your identities
Let's go to church immediately,
for the sake of Jesus Christ.
I missed Jesus Christ and his love.
Nice to meet you Nun Irene.
I am Priest Simon.
Eh.
Welcome, welcome but..
What do we owe this visit, Osman Bey?
I wanted to consolidate our friendship with you
so that we could become one man at heart
But I see...
...that there are those who
forged their friendship with you before us
Not at all, Osman Bey.
Let's say that whoever moved early
won the Bey's heart.
And of course we will all be together
against the infidels.
You are stroking your beard, Bayindir Bey.
Eyvallah, Eyvallah.
Give him his present.
May Allah bless you.
Thank you for your gift.
My gift is not just this
Boran.
I will give you four sites...
...of my property, Karasi Bey.
...with their taxes and people...
...they are under your control from now on.
We know very well how much suffering you
endured to obtain this property.
You do not give your property so easily,
so what prompted you to do so?
I need you on my side against
Commander Nayman.
And I ask for your help.
So you give me your property for this?
Correct
My only concern is the safety of my poeple.
For my people I take lands,
I give lands.
So, these sites are going
to belong to me.
Certainly
The location of the Black Tree and its
vicinity are all yours.
May Allah bless you
But I won't sacrifice my alps and my weapons for
a war we cannot win, Osman bey.
Well, what will your
father Kalemsah say about this?
My father is resting.
For a long time now
he counts my words as his words
Eyvallah (okay).
Father, those lands
are under Byzantium rule
Osman Bey?
True.
I knew from the start that
you wouldn't support me.
Now that I'm fighting Nayman alone,
Byzantium lands are yours.
Let the borders of (Byzantium) be yours then
While I am busy with them,
you'll watch my back.
You can't force me into this fire!
No.
I'm not forcing you into the fire.
Either you fight Byzantium.
Or you fight me.
While my homeland is on fire,
no one can sit comfortably in his palace.
Osman Bey, we also love to conquer.
No one gave us our property.
Whenever we mount our horses,
we lead them to the west and north
How do you think we got our lands, Uslu Bey?
We all have fought.
Now is the time to preserve
our acquired possessions.
You need to shut up. Don't trust your uncle.
Don't interfere with our conversation.
Look who is telling me to shut up!
I want to see your courage
on battlefield against Mongols.
Forget the Mongols!
Defend Inegol first,
which your father took with his own blood.
A man who couldn't defend his father's land
cannot talk to me like that.
- Uslu!
- Aktemur!
Stop.
Weigh your words before you speak them,
so that you do not exceed your limits.
Stop, Osman Bey,
we'll have a talk.
I haven't decided yet.
Make up your mind quickly,
Karasi Bey.
We respect you and want you to
support us.
You want us to support you
or fight you.
There is no other option.
Be my guest tonight
and I will tell you my decision at midnight.
Eyvallah (okay)
Eyvallah.
Uslu, prepare a room for
Osman Bey and his alps.
Host them in the best manner.
Osman Bey is a great Bey.
A brave Beys whose actions
match his words.
...but Aktemur.
His anger will put
mighty Osman Bey in a difficult position.
He did not hesitate in his words.
He is a barve man.
We made our offer.
Decision is yours, my Bey.
O Allah, O Allah!
My Allah! My Allah!
O Isra! O Isra! O Isra!
O Allah, O Allah!
My heart is burning, my heart is burning!
Extinguish this fire inside me, my Allah!
Help me my Allah!
Help my son.
My son!
My light!
He is slipping away, my Allah!
He is melting in front of my eyes!
I can't do anything for
my son, my Allah, please, you help him
Mitigate his pain.
Give him strength and health, please.
My Creator, my Creator, You don't give
anyone unbearable pain, my Allah.
This exam is so heavy!
Allah, this burden is too heavy for me!
Please help, please, give me my son!
Please, spare my son's life, my Allah.
You are the healer.
Grant healing to my son, O Allah,
grant healing to all our patients
Accept my prayers, please accept my prayers
Spare my son's life.
Amen, my Allah!
Amen, Amen!
Can I come in, daughter?
Of course, my sheik.
Come in.
In The Name of Allah Most Gracious Most Merciful.
Peace be upon you.
Peace be upon you, too my sheikh.
In The Name of Allah Most Gracious Most Merciful.
Please, daughter.
My sheikh!
Yes, our Allah who knows us
better than ourselves.
Didn't he say in his verse?
“And know that your wealth and your children are a trial,
and that God has a great reward with Him.”
So don't forget, my daughter, Malhun.
Children are exams.
Especially for a mother, the biggest test
is her children.
you know?
We get closer to our Lord the more our test grows
...I know, Sheikh, I know, but
My heart hurts so much.
He has the cure, daughter.
The One who gives the calamity has the cure.
Our hearts cannot be at peace
unless we turn to Him.
Think, Allah tested his prophets with
the most difficult tests
The ones who He loved the most.
Think about this even if your heart is burning.
And be patient in the best way, my daughter.
And I say this to myself...
be patient and be strong, but...
How will I be patient when the
exam is my son, my sheikh?
What strengthens patience is worship
Increase your worship and insist in your prayers
Ask, ask your Allah
Ask for heal, ask for relief
He does not turn His servants away from His door
What importance would
remain for us without our prayers?
Our servitude is hidden in
our worship and prayers, my daughter
We will first ask for good health for
our son Orhan from our Creator.
Inshallah.
This is an exam.
We will live with everything
that comes to us from our Creator.
We will not disobey.
We will consider everything that comes from
Him is beautiful.
We will say:
“You are the one who gave and you are the one who will take"
But we will keep our hearts strong as well.
Wasn't He the one who granted Eyup,
peace be upon him, the cure?
We will pray, daughter.
We will be patient.
Praise be to Allah, my sheikh, praise be to Allah.
My hope in my Creator
is not interrupted even for a moment.
His presence is on my tongue and in my heart.
I know my dear Orhan will be fine.
My Creator will heal him.
Inshallah.
Inegol Castle.
Cerkutay, what are we going to do now?
Watch me, do what I do.
They say something, what do they say?
We can't recite surahs!
Sing a song.
- A song?
- Yes
Bring henna, mother, bring henna, mother!
- Bring henna, mother.
- Ulgen!
Is my voice bad?
What?
Move your lips.
Okay.
Bring the henna, mother, bring the henna
Friends!
- Amen.
O Jesus Christ,
sanctify us with your love and light.
We promise to be as faithful to
you as to your disciples.
Hear our supplication, Amen.
- Amen.
May Jesus Christ accept your prayers.
My religion fellows!
It hasn't been long since I accepted
your religion.
But the love of Jesus inside me
is so strong.
I took Inegol from Turks.
Christianity will live its good
old days here again.
You play the biggest role in this.
Aladdin!
See, brother?
I can move my hand.
I told you, I told you Kumral Abdal
would heal you.
Come on, let's show it to our mothers.
Stop, stop, brother, don't get up so fast.
I will call them.
No, brother, I upset them, so let
us go to them.
This place will be the largest
and grandest church in this area
And the army that will fight for Jesus will be raised
in this church and in the monastery in Inegol
I called you for this.
You will do everything
in your hands for this cause.
Inegol will become one of
the centers of Christianity
Where do we start, Priest Hristo?
If your goal is to make
your army a true Christian army...
Your entire army must consist only Christians.
No other religion can be accepted.
Does everyone think this way?
Priest Hristo is right
The entire army must be Christian.
What about you?
Oh, the eye of the devil!
Jesus Christ, Holy Mary.
Don't get me wrong, this is my favorite church
I haven't been to in a long time.
May Jesus be pleased with you
Nun Irene is also
among my old students.
She grew up here too, in Ingol Abbey.
If so...
You must want the things I want
more than I do, Nun Irene.
We do very much!
Beautiful, beautiful.
Karesiogullari Beyship
Karesi Bey Mansion
- Here, my Bey.
- Give it to me, brother. Thanks.
My Bey, will Karasi Bey agree with us?
Thank Allah, thank Allah.
His heart and mind accepted
supporting us a long time ago.
All that remains is to hear and agree.
My Bey, I have the information.
In Karasi Beyshio, there is 6,000 alps.
I don't know how many of them will join.
As for Candar...
He has 3,000 alps maximum.
You're only talking about the qualified alps.
You don't count the sisters.
You don't count the elders.
When it's the war against infidels...
They will give us the double you say.
Still, we're not as half crowded as
Nayman, brother.
We can't fight Neyman without
Germiyans.
Many times,
a few defeated the many, Aykurt.
Don't worry.
We will have Germiyan Yakup Bey's
support, inshallah.
- Inshallah
- Inshallah.
How will this happen, my Bey?
We will act according to their mood, Gurbuz.
We did a lot of campaigns in order to
unite with a lot of Beys.
Inshallah, we have a move
for Germiyans as well.
If we have Germiyans as well,
the enemy must be worried!
Perhaps good resides in evil.
This won't be just a victory against Nayman.
Rather, it will be good for
the unity of our country, Inshallah.
- Inshallah.
- Inshallah, my Bey.
Inshallah.
Where's Aktemur?
Subasi went to check on the soldiers, my Bey.
You know, we're in foreign lands.
He wants everyone to be careful.
Yes, we are in foreign lands.
We shouldn't stay too far away.
Eyvallah my Bey.
There he is, Aktemur.
Come on, show yourself.
Aktemur Bey.
Uslu Bey wants to see you.
He set a table in his room for you.
Thank him.
But I'm not hungry.
Tell him I won't come.
It is the order of the Bey.
I can't go tell him you're not coming.
Please, my Bey.
Don't make Uslu Bey mad at me.
Okay.
Let's go and sit at your Bey's table.
This way, my Bey.
We interrogated everyone in the tribe
But no one
ever saw a stranger in
So, the traitor is among us.
Since Ismihan has connections everywhere,
she must be informed about our moves.
Mother.
Orhan.
I can move my hands.
I'm fine, Thank Allah.
Thank Allah.
Praise be to Allah, my son
Thank Allah!
My Allah!
Praise be!
Kumral Abdal's cure worked!
Orhan.
Mother.
Orhan!
- Orhan!
I can't feel any part of my body, mother!
Mother!
I can't move, mother!
Do something, mother.
esma, run and tell Komral Abdul.
Hurry!
Come on, hurry up, come on!
Mother I can't move! Mother1
Mother!
It will pass, it will pass,
Orhan, calm down, it will pass
I can't move, mother!
Mother!
What have you done
without my information, Bengi?
Using Esma as a spy?
I sent Esma just to
get news from the palace
Not to kill anyone
if I had known this would happen...
The one who is afraid of killing..
...cannot rule, Bengi Hatun.
This is a heavy statement, Mother Sultan.
We cannot pay for this sin.
Oktem Bey, you want to rule Kayi.
At the same time,
you want to stay away from blood.
If you want to rule, you will
stain your hands with blood and dirt.
Should Orhan die
in order to rule the Kayi?
You could have banished him
or find another solution...
What is this, Bengi Hatun?
Do you pity the enemy now?
In order for Aktemur to ascend the throne,
Osman's sons must be removed.
I say this for your own good.
What will happen to Orhan?
Will he die, Mother Sultan?
You two think I'm evil.
I am a mother too.
Orhan will not die.
He'll be worse than dead.
He will not be able to walk from now on.
Orhan will always be bedridden.
Can I come in, Uslu Bey?
Aktemur Bey is here.
Enter!
Uslu Bey.
Uslu Bey is dead.
He can't hear you.
Whose dog are you?
Who do you work for?
Forget who we are.
Soon we will be the brave alps
who saw how you killed Uslu Bey.
We'll be the alps who
will tell Karasi Bey about this.
You will not be able to reach your goal.
I will not allow this.
So, Osman Bey.
You convinced Candar Bey.
And you came to my palace and persuaded me
Tell me, how will you persuade Yakup Bey
in Germiyan city?
How are you going to convince that hard man?
We don't convince anyone.
He who does not have the fire of war
in his heart can never ignite it
We certainly erased a lot of hard men.
Yakup Bey's tribe has been fighting
the infidels for a hundred years.
Indeed, we have taken a huge mountain
like you against the enemy
Inshallah.
Inshallah, everything goes well
with Yakup Bey too.
Don't worry.
We will win.
Come on.
In The Name of Allah Most Gracious Most Merciful
May I come in, my Bey?
Enter!
Sir, we have heard sword sounds
in Uslu Bey's room.
The door is locked.
I considered you my son.
Uslu!
Aktemur, what's going on here?
It's a trick, my Bey!
They set up a trick!
What have you done, Aktemur?
You killed my son-in-law,
whom I consider my son!
No!
It is impossible for something like this
to happen where we are guests!
Your nephew couldn't take
the speech, Osman Bey!
For this reason, he shed my blood!
He burned my soul!
And I will kill him!
Nothing like this will happen!
Aktemur is not such a man.
But if you still want to fight.
You must kill me first.
Visit our website for more: turkision.com